reghelper.com 2019-06-26

# SafeApp Software, LLC - Keep Your Computer Running FAST And Working RIGHT

Privacy Policy  
---  
   
**Version 2.2 Effective June 23, 2014**  
   
Your privacy is very important to us. Safe _App_ Software, LLC ("Safe _App_ Software" or "We" or "Our") is committed to privacy and security and protecting the personal information that you provide to us. This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how we collect and use information from visitors to our website, including those who download and install our software, what we do with the information we collect, and the choices you have concerning the collection and use of such information. This Privacy Policy applies to [www.SafeAppSoftware.com](http://www.safeappsoftware.com/), [www.RegHelper.com](http://www.safeappsoftware.com/rh/default.asp), [www.SASDiskCleaner.com](http://www.safeappsoftware.com/dc/default.asp), [www.ComputerUpdater.com](http://www.safeappsoftware.com/cu/default.asp) (the "Site") and all versions of the software applications as updated and amended from time to time (the "Software").

This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors who access our Site and/or the Software. Collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal information may be subject to different regulations outside the United States. Regardless, you agree to be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

By accessing the Site and/or the Software or providing information requested by the Site and/or the Software, or by continuing to use the Site or Software after having an opportunity to review this Privacy Policy, you have consented to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our use of the information collected. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Site or the Software.   

**1. _Overview_.**

  * Information Collected
  * Use of Collected Information
  * Cookies
  * Remarketing
  * Security of Collected Information
  * Children
  * Your Choices/Opt-Out
  * Consent
  * External Links Disclaimer
  * Disclaimer of Liability
  * Contact Information
  * Revisions to this Privacy Policy/Opt-Out

**2. _Information Collected_.**

 _Access and Aggregate Information_. In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about you. Like most standard web site services, we use log files. Our web servers collect the domain or “IP address” of visitors, browser type, type of computer, search engines used, referring/exit pages, operating systems used, type of Web browser used, aggregate information on pages accessed on the Site and statistical information related to our products and the performance of our products, and broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Our web servers also seek (as many web sites do) to place a “cookie” (a small data file) on your computer’s hard drive which allows the server to determine your computer when it visits again. This cookie is not used to store any personally identifiable information. For more information on cookies, please  click here.

 _Software Installation_. During the download process and/or installation of the Software, you will be asked to provide personally identifiable information, including your name and e-mail address. We use this information to contact you by e-mail regarding your installation, registration, updates, and send you special offers from us and trusted third parties. Your e-mail address is not shared with these trusted third parties. Your personal information provided during installation will be stored in our database, along with other information collected during the installation process and by our cookies (e.g., link to referring site, e-mail, or advertisement, IP address, browser capabilities, and total Invalid Entries, Junk Files, or Available Updates).

 _Software Registration_. When upgrading the Software to the full version, you will be asked to provide personally identifiable information, including e-mail address, your name, and additional contact information (ie, telephone number and home address) and billing information (such as a credit card number and expiration date). Your personal information provided during installation will be stored in our database, along with other information collected during the installation process and by our cookies (e.g., link to referring site, e-mail, or advertisement, IP address, browser capabilities, and total Invalid Entries, Junk Files, or Available Updates). Any credit card numbers provided to us will only be stored for as long as necessary to complete the transaction. In the event that we use a third party service provided for processing credit card payments, your credit card information will not be transferred to us and will be subject to such third party’s privacy policy. This information will be stored in our database along with other information collected by our cookies and during the installation and/or registration process. For more information on the types of information collected by our cookies, please  click here.

 _Contacts_. When you contact us or send e-mail inquiries to us, we may keep a record of this communication. Additionally, the return e-mail address is used to answer the e-mail inquiry we receive. We do not share the return e-mail address with any third party, however we may use the e-mail address for other business related purposes.

 _Voluntary Customer Surveys_. We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage you to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personally identifiable information will remain confidential. Participation in our surveys is voluntary.

We take the information we receive from individuals responding to our surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other users to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information).  

**3. _Use of Collected Information_.**

 _Aggregate Information_. Domain name information and other aggregate information and non-personally identifiable information that we collect is aggregated to measure such things as the number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our Site. Additionally, we use aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

 _Personally Identifiable Information_. Personally identifiable information collected is used for purposes specific to the Site and/or the Software, including marketing and promotional purposes, statistical analysis of behavior, product development, content improvement, and editorial and feedback purposes. Personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise at the time of collection or in special circumstances which are detailed below. Aggregate information that we collect from you is stored on our servers with your personally identifiable information.

 _Third Party Vendors_. We may share your personally identifiable information with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies are contractually bound to use such personally identifiable information we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide. From time to time we may contract with third party payment processors to handle credit card transactions. Your credit card information will not be transferred by such third party to us and will at all times be subject to such third party’s privacy policy.

 _Written Direction_. We will release information about you if you direct us to do so in writing.

 _Communication_. We send all users who initiate the installation process and/or complete the installation process e-mail messages and advertisements regarding the Software. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see <http://www.safeappsoftware.com/regunsub.asp> for more information on your ability to opt-out of future commercial e-mail messages. Additionally, on rare occasions, it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications.

 _Special Cases/Legal Disclaimer_. It is our policy not to use or share personal information about you in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, we may disclose personal information about you, or information regarding your use of the product, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our licenses or other user policies; to operate the product properly; or to protect Safe _App_ Software or our users.

 _E-Mail Suppression Lists_. We may disclose a user’s e-mail address as part of a suppression file or do-not-e-mail list to make sure that your unsubscribe requests are forwarded to the appropriate parties to ensure removal of e-mail databases in compliance with the Can-Spam Act of 2003.

 _Sale, Merger or Asset Transfer_. We may buy other business or their assets or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that we purchase or all of our assets are acquired, user information, including information collected through the Site or the installation or use of the Software would be on of the transferred assets.  

**4. _"Cookies"_.**

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once you close your browser, the cookie will terminate. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in you Internet browser’s help file.

We use cookies for information collection purposes including, without limitation, to estimate audience size, track visits, measure traffic patterns, monitor referring/exit pages, identify web browsers, identify types of computer used, record number of Invalid Entries, Junk Files, or Available Updates, advertisement leads and additional information collection features. Our cookies are not used to store your personally identifiable information, however, information recorded by our cookies will be stored in our database and associated with your personally identifiable information. Our use of cookies does not enable third parties to access any of your personally identifiable information.

Some of our advertisers and partners may also use cookies on our Site. We have no control over their cookies, the information collected and its use.  

**5. _Remarketing_.**

We use remarketing to advertise to our users online. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads across sites on the Internet. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your past visits to our web site. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).  

**6. _Security of Collected Information_.**

This Site takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the Site, their information is protected both online and offline. When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked or open when users are just surfing.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information offline. The data center which provides our web hosting services is an SAS-70 Level II Certified facility.

While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third party hackers from illegally obtaining this information.  

**7. _Children_.**

The Site is not intended for use by children. We do not allow persons under the age of 13 to register to use the Software. We do not knowingly collect information about children under 13. We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the web sites that their children visit. The Federal Trade Commission regulates the means by which web site operators collect and use personal information from children under age 13, pursuant to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (the "Act"). For more information about the Act and children’s on-line privacy in general, visit the FTC’s web site at <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy>.  

**8. _Your Choices/Opt-Out_.**

Users who no longer wish to receive our advertising or promotional communications can click on the opt-out mechanism provided in the e-mail communication, or fill out our unsubscribe form at <http://www.safeappsoftware.com/regunsub.asp>, or the user may contact us at <http://www.safeappsoftware.com/email.asp>.

Users of our Site are always notified when their information is being collected by an outside party. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.  

**9. _Consent_.**

By providing the information requested by the Site, or by continuing to use the Site or the Software after having an opportunity to review this Privacy Policy, you have consented to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and Safe _App_ Software’s use of the information it collected as described at the point of collection or in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Site or the Software.  

**10. _External Links Disclaimer_.**

This Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Site.  

**11. _Disclaimer of Liability_.**

Under no circumstances shall Safe _App_ Software be liable for any damages, including, but not limited to, special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damage that result from the use of the Site, even if Safe _App_ Software has been advised of the possibility of such damages. This and other sections in the Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with, and are subject to, our End User License Agreement for the Software.  

**12. _Contact Information_.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at:

> Safe _App_ Software, LLC  
> 600 Mamaroneck Avenue, Suite 400  
> Harrison, New York 10528  
> Phone: 1-914-341-2587  
> E-mail: <http://www.safeappsoftware.com/email.asp>

We welcome your questions and/or suggestions about our Privacy Policy.  

**13. _Revisions to this Privacy Policy/Opt-Out_.**

Safe _App_ Software reserves the right to revise, amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in any manner. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Site to notify you of these changes. Where practicable, we will provide you with the ability to opt-out of these new uses. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. By accessing the Site or using the Software after modification of the Privacy Policy, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy as modified. The last date this Privacy Policy was revised is set forth above.
